<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thermos</string>
    <string name="setup_info">Make setup fast and easy by using your Fitbit profile! \nJust tap to enable, sign into your Fitbit account, and \nwe will use the information you already provided to \nFitbit to create your Thermos Smart Lid app profile. \n\nYour hydration stats will automatically be synced \nfrom your Thermos Smart Lid app to your Fitbit \naccount each time you finish a bottle of water.</string>
    <string name="emailRegisterInfo">Enter your email address to receive emails containing updates, notices, and promotions about this mobile app and Thermos products. You can withdraw your consent at any time by using the unsubscribe function in each with certain third parties in line with our <a href="http://www.thermos.com/privacy-policy.aspx">Privacy Policy</a> For more details, please refer to our Privacy Policy or <a href="http://www.thermos.com/contact.aspx">Contact Us</a></string>
    <string name="wake_up_lid_info">Use the enclosed charger to plug your Smart Lid inot a power source, such as a computer or wall adapter. Once the lid has power, it will wake up immediately.</string>
    <string name="fitbit_enable_info">Your Thermos Smart Lid app profile has officially been populated with your Fitbit data. Continue through set up. Update any information you like.</string>
    <string name="hydration_goal">Your hydration goal is set to the general baselinegoal ,which is provided for informational purposes only. Filling out a hydration profile will create a Suggested Hydration Goal catered to you and  your lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="skip_profile_setup">Skip Profile Setup.</string>
    <string name="limit_exceeded">Can select a maximum of %d images</string>
    <string name="already_selected" formatted="false">you already selected %d images (%d/1)</string>
    <string name="six_photo_string">please select 1 photos</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="title_fitbit_authentication">Fitbit</string>

    <!--sharedpreference-->
    <string name="preference_file_key">com.thermos.wistron.sharedpreferences</string>
    <string name="preference_user_name">preference_user_name</string>
    <string name="preference_user_photo_real_path">preference_user_photo_real_path</string>
    <string name="preference_user_email">preference_user_email</string>
    <string name="preference_user_fitbit_access_token">preference_user_fitbit_access_token</string>
    <string name="preference_user_fitbit_user_id">preference_user_fitbit_user_id</string>
    <string name="preference_user_waterUnit">preference_user_waterUnit</string>

</resources>
